NICOLAS NOMAL

JUNIOR
FULL STACK
DEVELOPER



DEVELOPMENT SKILLS

HTML 5	CSS 3	JAVASCRIPT
JQUERY	ANGULAR	REACT
MVC	SCRUM	XALA
PHP/SQL	LARAVEL	SYMFONY
WORDPRESS	ООР	GIT/GITHUB

EDUCATION

Full stack developer

NUMERICALL (ESCH/ALZETTE, LUXEMBOURG) 09/2020-12/2020

- 490 hours bootcamp spread over 3.5 months
- Technologies/languages: check the skills section on the left
- WebForce3 Certifications: Web development techniques (RS1448)
 - Web integration techniques (RS1447)

CONTACT INFO

- +33 6 32 01 92 46 8 rue Beving L-1234 Luxembourg
- nicolasnomalpro@gmail.com
- in LinkedIn: @nicolasnomalwebdev

Advanced technician's certificate in IT

AKOR ALTERNANCE (PARIS, FRANCE) DIPLOMA OBTAINED IN 2004

- Specialized in network management
- Sandwich course 3 days at school/2 days in the company.

A-Levels, economic and social sector

LYCÉE A.EINSTEIN (ESSONNE, FRANCE) DIPLOMA OBTAINED IN 1999

ABOUT ME

I have always been passionate by IT and web. Back to 2000-2005 i used to create my own html and flash websites. I then chose other ways but now that I finished successfully my 490 hours intensive bootcamp, I am sure that this job is made for me! I am a fast learner and I love problem-solving. I am open to learn new languages, frameworks and technologies I don't know. As for my soft skills, I like people and I know how to adapt to new teams. I am not afraid to speak in public and take decisions if needed.

I am available right now and really want to succeed, why not with you?

IT RELATED JOBS 6 years



2018-2019

LA CAVE À FROMAGES (LUXEMBOURG)

Multi-skilled employee Creation of the website, graphic creation, IT helpdesk, emailing, Facebook page community manager

2007-2008

A.D.I. (ORSAY 91)

Itinerant IT technician

2009

JEVIDA (TOULOUSE 31)

Salesman

Website sales, SEO, online video games Project manager for the conception of a poker video game sold to a subcontractor of Microsoft France.

2009

TOP TECHNOLOGY (TOULOUSE 31)

Salesman for websites (one shot)

2005-2006

PC CITY (VILLEBON/YVETTE 91)

IT Salesman (B2B and B2C)

2005

PC CITY (VILLEBON/YVETTE 91)

Customer care agent (after sales IT service)

2002-2004

PC CITY (VILLEBON/YVETTE 91)

IT Technician (after sales IT service)
Advanced technician's certificate in IT
Sandwich course
3 days at school/2 days in the company.
IT Help Desk activities
Software and hardware
OS installations (Windows and MacOS)

SALESMAN 8 years



2011-2012

GAN PRÉVOYANCE (TOULOUSE 31)

Itinerant insurance salesman

2009-2010

TELEPERFORMANCE- SFR (TOULOUSE 31)

Telemarketer

2009

ARAMIS AUTO (MURET 31)

Car salesman

2008

FITNESS FIRST (STE GENEVIÈVE DES BOIS 91)

Salesman in a fitness gym

2006-2007

COLISEE FINANCE (ST MAUR DES FOSSES 94)

Independent real estate agent specialized in defiscalisation

OTHER EXPERIENCES
8 years



2019-2020

KINÉPOD (LUXEMBOURG)

Orthopaedic technician

2015-2017

PRODUCTIONS TV (PARIS/USA/JAPON)

Show-business artist

2012-2015

KLÉSIA/GROUPE MORNAY (TOULOUSE 31)

Call agent for a provident institution

2000-2002

MC DONALD'S (PARIS 75)

Polyvalent employee

LANGUAGES

French: native language English: very good Spanish: good Italian: average

INTERESTS

Muay thai boxing Horse Riding